<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<vxml version="2.1">
   <menu id="languageChoice" dtmf="true">
      <prompt>
	  	 Welcome to artemisia VoiceNet, this is an information platform about artemisia.
         Please choose your language: Press 1 for English or 2 for French.
      </prompt>
      <prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
	  	 Bienvenue sur Artemesia VoiceNet, ceci est une plateforme d'informations sur l'artémisia.
         Veuillez choisir votre langue : Appuyez 1 pour l'anglais ou 2 pour le français.
      </prompt>
    <choice next="#englishPrompt"/>
	<choice next="#frenchPrompt"/>
    </menu>
	
   <!-- English Prompt Block -->
   <menu id="englishPrompt" dtmf="true">
      	<prompt>
		You've entered the English menu. For providing farmers input or receiving farmers information, press 1. For receiving sales information, press 2
        </prompt>
	    <choice next="#efarmerMenu"/>
	    <choice next="#eSalesForm"/>
   </menu>

   <form id="eSalesForm">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		   here an audio should be played with information about the sales <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#englishPrompt" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <menu id="efarmerMenu" dtmf="true">
	<prompt>
	   You've entered the farmers menu providing different types of information, or for submitting answers and questions to the platform. 
       Press 1 for weather information. 
       Press 2 for general farming information.
       Press 3 for answers and tips to last weeks questions.
       Press 4 for asking a pressing question about the farming of artemesia plants to other farmers. 
       Press 5 for helping other farmers with answering pressing questions. 
       Press 6 for submitting sales information. Press 7 to return to the previous menu.
    </prompt>
	<choice next="#eWeather"/>
	<choice next="#eGeneral"/>
	<choice next="#eAnswers"/>
	<choice next="#eQuestions"/>
    <choice next="#efarmerQuestions"/>
	<choice next="#eSales"/>
	<choice next="#englishPrompt"/>
    </menu>

   <form id="eWeather">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		 This is information about the weather in Bamako <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next= "https://ict4d.altervista.org/weather.php"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <menu id="eGeneral" dtmf="true">
		<prompt>
		  This is a menu for general information about the production and farmer techniques for growing and planting the artemesia seeds. 
          Press 1 for information about best practices to grow artemesia. Press 2 for information about the chemicals to use. 
          Press 3 to return to the main menu <break/>
		</prompt>
		<choice next="#egrowingPlant"/>
	    <choice next="#echemicals"/>
	    <choice next="#efarmerMenu"/>
   </menu>

   <form id="egrowingPlant">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		  This is information on how to grow the plant, providing basic steps and best practices and products<break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#eGeneral"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="echemicals">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		    This is information about what chemicals to use, and what are dangerous with some simple considerations. <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#eGeneral"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="eAnswers">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		  Here a recording should be played of answers to previous questions <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next= "https://ict4d.altervista.org/Play_multiple_audio_from_folder.php"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="eQuestions">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		   A recording will be made of your pressing question <break/>
		</prompt>
        <goto next="record.xml"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="efarmerQuestions">
	<block>
		<prompt>
		  Here a recording is played of pressing questions <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next= "https://ict4d.altervista.org/English/Questions/play.php"/>
    </block>
	</form>

	<form id="eanswerto">
    <field name="answer">
        <prompt>
		  Press 1 to answer one of the questions. Press 2 to listen to the questions again. Press 3 to return to the previous menu. 
        </prompt>
        <grammar mode="dtmf" root="acc">
                <rule id="acc" scope="public">
                    <one-of>
                        <item>1</item>
                        <item>2</item>
                        <item>3</item>
                    </one-of>
                </rule>
        </grammar> 
    </field>
    <filled>
            <if cond="answer == 1">
                <goto next="recordAnswer.xml"/>
            <elseif cond="answer == 2"/>
                <goto next="#efarmerQuestions"/>
            <elseif cond="answer == 3"/>
                <goto next="#efarmerMenu"/>
            </if>
    </filled>
   </form>

   <form id="eSales">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		  A recording will be made stating the sales information of your farm. This includes information
          about the stock of the artemesia, the price, and the location of the farm. <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="salesrecord.xml" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <!-- French Prompt Block -->
   <menu id="frenchPrompt" dtmf="true">
       <prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
		Vous êtes dans le menu francais. Pour donner des informations sur les agriculteurs ou recevoir des informations sur les agriculteurs, appuyez sur 1. Pour recevoir des informations sur les ventes, appuyez sur 2.
	</prompt>
    <choice next="#ffarmerMenu"/>
    <choice next="#fSalesForm"/>
   </menu>

   <form id="fSalesForm">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		   here an audio should be played with information about the sales <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#frenchPrompt" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <menu id="ffarmerMenu" dtmf="true">
	<prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
	   Ceci est le menu des agriculteurs offrant différents types d'informations. Appuyez sur 1 pour les informations météorologiques, appuyez sur 2 pour les informations générales sur l'agriculture, appuyez sur 3 pour les réponses et conseils aux questions de la semaine dernière, appuyez sur 4 pour poser une question d'agriculteur. Appuyez sur 5 pour aider d'autres agriculteurs à répondre à des questions urgentes. Appuyez sur 6 pour soumettre des informations de vente. Appuyez sur 7 pour revenir au menu précédent.
        </prompt>
	<choice next="#fWeather"/>
	<choice next="#fGeneral"/>
	<choice next="#fAnswers"/>
	<choice next="#fQuestions"/>
    <choice next="ffarmerQuestions"/>
	<choice next="#fSales"/>
	<choice next="#frenchPrompt"/>
    </menu>

   <form id="fWeather">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		This is information about the weather <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#ffarmerMenu" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <menu id="fGeneral" dtmf="true">
		<prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
		  Ceci est un menu pour des informations générales sur la production et les techniques agricoles pour la culture et la plantation des graines d'artémisia. Appuyez sur 1 pour des informations sur les meilleures pratiques pour cultiver l'artémisia. Appuyez sur 2 pour des informations sur les produits chimiques à utiliser. Appuyez sur 3 pour revenir au menu principal.<break/>
		</prompt>
		<choice next="#fgrowingPlant"/>
	    <choice next="#fchemicals"/>
	    <choice next="#ffarmerMenu"/>
   </menu>

   <form id="fgrowingPlant">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		This is inormation on how to grow the plant, providing basic steps and best practices and products<break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#fGeneral" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="fchemicals">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		This is information about what chemicals to use, and what are dangerous with some simple considerations. <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#fGeneral" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="fAnswers">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		  Here a recording should be played of answers to previous questions <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="#ffarmerMenu" />
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="fQuestions">
	<block> 
		<prompt>
		  Here a recording is made of pressing questions <break/>
		</prompt>
        <goto next="recordf.xml"/>
	</block>
   </form>

   <form id="ffarmerQuestions">
	<block>
		<prompt>
		  Here a recording is played of pressing questions <break/>
		</prompt>
    </block>
    <field name="answer">
        <prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
		  Appuyez sur 1 pour répondre à l'une des questions. Appuyez sur 2 pour écouter à nouveau les questions. Appuyez sur 3 pour revenir au menu précédent. 
        </prompt>
        <grammar mode="dtmf" root="acc">
                <rule id="acc" scope="public">
                    <one-of>
                        <item>1</item>
                        <item>2</item>
                        <item>3</item>
                    </one-of>
                </rule>
        </grammar> 
    </field>
    <filled>
            <if cond="answer == 1">
                <goto next="recordAnswer.xml"/>
            <elseif cond="answer == 2"/>
                <goto next="#ffarmerQuestions"/>
            <elseif cond="answer == 3"/>
                <goto next="ffarmerMenu"/>
            </if>
    </filled>
   </form>

   <form id="fSales">
	<block> 
		<prompt xml:lang="fr-fr">
		  Un enregistrement sera effectué pour indiquer les informations de vente de votre ferme. Cela inclut des informations sur le stock d'artémésia, le prix, et la localisation de la ferme. <break/>
		</prompt>
		<goto next="fsalesrecord.xml" />
	</block>
   </form>
</vxml>
